<?xml version="1.0"?>
<galleries>
	<settings> 
        <background>0xe1c8bc</background>
        <fontcolor>0x666666</fontcolor>
        <fontsize>26</fontsize>
        <font>Nuptial BT</font>
		<interval>0</interval>
		<Leftspacing>30</Leftspacing>
		<Topspacing>25</Topspacing>
		<Linespacing>-10</Linespacing>
    </settings> 
	
	<slide>
    	<data> &nbsp; &nbsp;</data>
		<data>     "It is nice to be important, but it is more important to be nice." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>    "Seasons change all the times but the love should never be seasonal.   </data>
		<data>                     		It should go on and on and on."               </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>      	  "You don't get to choose how you're going to die, or when; </data>
		<data>          	     You can only decide how you're going to live now."   </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>             "We tend to be more as a doctor rather than a patient;  </data>
		<data>         seek first to understand rather than seeking to be understood." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>     		"Satisfaction of a desire is like a night”s sleep, </data>
		<data>       		When we wake up a new desire crops up." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>       "If you can not become a candle then at least become a mirror    </data>
		<data>                 so that you can spread the light of the candle."       </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>   	"There can never be enough darkness anywhere in the world   </data>
		<data>          		 that a single lit lamp cannot eliminate."   </data>
		<data>   </data>
    </slide>

 <slide>
    	<data>             "Spend more and more time in rectifying yourself so that </data>
		<data>                you have lesser and lesser time in criticizing others." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>                    "If love is your greatest weakness then you are    </data>
		<data>                           the strongest person in the world."      </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>             "Things were made to Use and Men were made to Love,   </data>
		<data>              but men are being used and Things are being loved."   </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>      	"The real value of Money is felt only after you actually spend it  </data>   <!-- "The real value of Money is felt only after you actually spend it" similarly "The real value of Brahma Gyan is experienced only after you have adopted it in your daily life"  /-->
		<data>          	 similarly the real value of Brahma Gyan is experienced </data>
		<data>               only after you have adopted it in your daily life."</data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>    "You may respect all the family memebers as the  images of almighty  </data>
		<data>      nirankar.If one member bows the other will bow automatically."  </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>&nbsp; &nbsp;</data>
		<data> "Forgiveness is the sweet scent that a flower gives when it is being crushed." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>     "Human beings are not happy with what God has bestowed to them   </data>
		<data>      They show their unhappiness on what God has bestowed on others." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>               "Some one asked True Master ,   I Want Peace” .  </data>
		<data>           Master replied , Remove 'I' & 'Want' , you'll have Peace”." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	<data>                  "The best portion of a  man's life is his little,    </data>
		<data>                nameless unremembered acts of kindness and  love."     </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>                     "Some flowers grow best in the sun, others </data>
		<data>                       do well in the shade ! God always knows </data>
		<data>                   what is best for us and puts us where we grow best."</data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>               "Divine knowledge can never stay in one’s heart unless    </data>
		<data>                        there is faith in the True Master."     </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	<data>              "One spark is sufficient to burn the whole heap of dry grass;     </data>
		<data>                              likewise,a single drop of divine </data>
		<data>                              grace is enough to wipe all sins."</data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>         	"Success is not in being the best and winning the race,    </data>
		<data>        	but its in handling the worst and finishing the race."     </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>                "We love ourselves even after doing many mistakes,      </data>
		<data>               Then how we can hate others for their small mistakes"     </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

 <slide>
    	<data>   "We should always remember that when we point one finger at a person,  </data>
		<data>                	the other fingers are pointing at ourselves" </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>       "Success is not a matter of being the best and winning the race, </data>
		<data>      success is a matter of handling the worst and finishing the race."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>                      "Everything that irritates us about others      </data>
		<data>                    can lead us to an understanding of ourselves."     </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data> &nbsp; &nbsp; </data>
		<data>    "When a person makes his mind the dwelling of God, he is all bliss." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	<data>                  "Those who have failed to work toward the truth   </data>
		<data>                	  have missed the purpose of living."    </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data> &nbsp;  &nbsp;</data>
		<data>                 "If you do not conquer self, you will be conquered by self."     </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>          "God has editing rights over our prayers. He will...edit them,  </data>
		<data>             correct them, bring them in line with His will and       </data>
		<data>                then hand them back to us to be resubmitted."    </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>                 "A sound mind in a sound body, is a short, but    </data>
		<data>               full description of a happy state in this world."  </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data> &nbsp;  &nbsp; </data>
		<data>          "The question is not how one died but the question is how one lived."        </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>      	"What lies behind us and what lies before us are tiny matters   </data>
		<data>             	  compared to what lies within us!!"   </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data> "Always be a reason for someone’s happiness and may not be a part of this. </data>
		<data>    Always be a part of someone’s sadness and never be a reason of it."        </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>  "No matter what anyone does to you, no one can take away from you your </data>
		<data>  capacity to do good. You lose it only by willingly giving it up yourself." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	<data>        "You have reached the pinnacle of success as soon as you become  </data>
		<data>               uninterested in money, compliments, or publicity." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>         "Those who serve the best, reap the most emotionally, physically,    </data>
		<data>            mentally, and spiritually. They attain highest dimensions </data>
		<data>                  of inner peace and outer fullfillment."</data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	<data>      "If things happen your way, you are lucky, but if they don't then   </data>
		<data>         you are very lucky because it is according to God's wish." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	<data>                "God is the ocean of virtues.If you are burning </data>
		<data>                     with vice, take a dip in that ocean."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	<data> &nbsp; &nbsp;</data>
		<data>          "A house is built by hands but a home is built by hearts"  </data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	<data>  "As mathematics has some formulas to solve the sums, sameway the True </data>
		<data>       Master gives us formulas to live happy and peaceful life."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>    "The important thing is not so much that every child should be taught,</data>
		<data>            as that every child should be given the wish to learn."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>       "Have the determination of a mirror...It never loses its ability</data>
		<data>          to reflect, even if it is broken into thousand pieces."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>              "Cheerfulness keeps up the spirit of one who possesses  </data>
		<data>                  it and brings a smile to the lips of others."   </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	<data>       "Our life begins with our cry, Our life ends with others cry , </data>
		<data>   Try to utilize this gap and laugh as much as possible between these cries."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	
		<data> &nbsp;&nbsp; </data>
		<data>       "Mankind must put an end to war, or war will put an end to mankind." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	
		<data> &nbsp;&nbsp; </data>
		<data>      "I cried because I had no shoes till I saw a man with no feet."  </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>           "One machine can do the work of fifty ordinary men.    </data>
		<data>          No machine can do the work of one extraordinary man."  </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	
		<data> &nbsp;&nbsp;  </data>
		<data>        "We shall never know all the good that a simple smile can do." </data>
		
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>                     "What is the worse thing than loosing sight?       </data>
		<data>                 Worse thing than loosing sight is to loose vision."     </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>              "The only way of finding the limits of the possible is  </data>
		<data>                   by going beyond them into the impossible."  </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>


<slide>
    	
		<data> &nbsp;&nbsp;</data>
		<data>    "You were born with wings. Why prefer to crawl through life.." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>      "Give thousands of chances to your enemy to become your friend,  </data>
		<data>         but give no chance to your friend to become your enemy." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
	<data>     "If someone feels that they had never made a mistake in their life, </data>
		<data>    then it means they had never tried a new thing in their life." </data>
		<data> </data>
		</slide>

<slide>
    	<data>          "Cherish what you have, and Plan what to gain because past  </data>
		<data>                 never returns but future may return the loss." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>         "To see the wrongs of others is the root of all evils,</data>
		<data>     	To see one's own wrongs is the gate to the myriad virtues."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>        "The true saints and devotees of God proclaim only one thing; that,</data>
		<data>           even the wisest will drown, if they forsake devotion of God."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>     "Purity in thought, speech, and act is absolutely necessary for anyone </data>
		<data>                   	     to be religious. Purity is strength."    </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>                      "When one door closes, another opens; </data>
		<data>         but we often look so long and so regretfully upon the closed </data>
		<data>             door that we do not see the one which has opened for us."</data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>            "If you don't go after what you want, you'll never have it.</data>
		<data>                    If you don't ask, the answer is always no.</data>
		<data>            If you don't step forward, you're always in the same place."</data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>"Apologizing doesn't mean that merely you are wrong and the others right, </data>
		<data>  It also means that you value the relationship much more than your ego."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>     "Forget your own unhappiness by creating a little happiness for others </data>
		<data>        because when you are good to others you are best to yourself"</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>     "Failure is not a terrible or shameful thing. It is a stepping stone</data>
		<data>      to success. If every failure is treated as a learning experience,</data>
		<data>                            it will finally help us succeed."   </data>
   </slide>


<slide>
    <data>"Make a mind which never minds. Make a heart which never hurts. Make</data>
		<data>     a touch which never pains & make a relation which never ends."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>    "Treat everyone with Love, even those who are rude to you; not because</data>
		<data>                     they are not nice, but because you are nice."   </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>       "Fear less, hope more; Whine less, breathe more; Talk less, </data>
		<data>     say more; Hate less, love more; And all good things are yours."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>    "One spark is sufficient to burn the whole heap of dry grass; likewise</data>
		<data>          a single drop of divine grace is enough to wipe all sins."</data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	<data>             "Happiness resides not in posessions and not in gold;      </data>
		<data>                 the feeling of happiness dwells in the soul."      </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	
		<data>&nbsp;&nbsp;</data>
		<data>     "The weak can never forgive. Forgiveness is the attribute of the strong." </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

<slide>
    	
		<data>&nbsp;&nbsp;</data>
		<data>  "Love cures people, the ones who receive love and the ones who give it, too." </data>
		<data> </data>
		
    </slide>

<slide>
    	
		<data>&nbsp;&nbsp;</data>
		<data>                             "Think globally but act locally."    </data>
		<data> </data>
    </slide>

</galleries>






	
	
	
	
	
		

